friendsite.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy | dropspace.io

  1. #### Introduction

    1. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our service visitors; in this policy, we explain how we will treat your personal information
    2. By using our service, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of the policy
  2. #### Collecting Personal Information

    1. We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information: 
      1. Information about your computer and about your visits to and use of the service (including but limited to: your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths);
      2. Information that you provide to us when registering with the service (including but not limited to: email address, name and a password. Or if using any third-party required information necessary for account creation and use)
      3. Information that you provide when completing your profile on the service (including but not limited to your name, profile photos, gender, date of birth, interests and hobbies, educational and employment details)
      4. Information that you provide to us when using the service or that is generated in the course of using the service
      5. Information that you post via the service for publication on the internet
      6. Information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us or through the service
      7. Information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and / or newsletters (including your name and email address)
and 
      8. Any other personal information that you choose to add to the service
    2. Before you disclose to us the personal information of another person, you must obtain the persons consent to both the disclosure and the processing of that personal information in accordance with this policy
  3. #### Using Personal Information

    1. Personal information submitted to us through the service will be used for the purposes specified in this policy or on the relevant pages of the website
    2. We may use your personal information to: 
      1. Administer the service and the business
      2. Personalize the service for you
      3. Enable your use of the social networking services and third-party services available on this service
      4. Send you non-marketing commercial communications
      5. Send you email notifications that you have specifically requested or required to operate the service
      6. Provide third-parties with statistical information about our users, limiting as much personal information as possible
      7. Deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the service
      8. Keep the website secure and prevent fraud
and 
      9. Verify compliances with the terms and conditions governing the use of the service (including monitoring private messages and comments sent through our service for the sole purpose of preventing misuse)
    3. If you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us
    4. Your privacy settings can be used to limit the publication of your information on our website, and can be adjusted using privacy controls on the website. Whilst we take all best endeavors to keep your personal information private, you should not post anything that should not be seen or disclosed publicly
    5. We will not, without your express consent, supply your personal information to any third-party for the purpose of their, or any other third-parties direct marketing. We may sell your information only upon sale, transfer, bankruptcy, liquidation of the company
  4. #### Disclosing Personal Information

    1. We may disclose your personal information to any of our employees, officers, insurers, professional advisors, agents, suppliers, subcontractors, service administrators & operators, resellers insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy
    2. We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group of companies (meaning any subsidiaries, our holding company and all its subsidiaries) insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy
    3. We may disclose your personal information: 
      1. to the extent that we are required to do so by law
      2. in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings
      3. in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk
      4. To the purchaser or prospective purchaser of any business or asset that we are, or are contemplating selling
and 
      5. To any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonably opinion, such court or authority would reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information
    4. Except as provided in this policy, we will not provide your personal information to third parties
  5. #### International Data Transfers

    1. Information that we may collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries we operate in order to to enable us to use the information in accordance with this policy
    2. Information that we collect maybe transferred to the following countries which do not have the data protection laws equivalent to those in force in Canada: The United States of America, Russia, Japan, China and India
    3. Personal information that you publish on the service or submit for publication may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others
    4. You expressly agree to the transfers of information within this section
  6. #### Retaining Personal Information

    1. This section sets out our data retention policies and procedure, which are designed to help ensure that we comply with our legal obligations in relation to the retention and deletion of personal information
    2. Personal information that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes
    3. Without prejudice, we will usually delete personal data when you choose to delete that data, or when you cancel your membership to the service. Copies of your personal information may be retained for the purposes of system backup, your agree that we may retain that personal information and use it only as necessary within the policy
    4. Notwithstanding the other provisions of this section, we will retain documents and files containing personal information: 
      1. to the extent that we are required to do so by law
      2. if we believe that the documents may be relevant to any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings
      3. and 
      4. in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk)
  7. #### Security of Your Information

    1. We will take reasonable technical and organization precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information
    2. We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password and firewall-protected) servers
    3. You acknowledge that the transmission of information over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet
    4. You are responsible for keeping your password and other login details confidential. We will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to the website)
    5. Any object that you upload is publically available, it has a unique url which will make it difficult to guess, but anyone knowing this url can access it, despite privacy settings.
  8. #### Children

    1. If you are under the age of majority applicable where you are resident, you may only use this service and disclose any personal information with your parent’s or guardian’s express consent. 
    2. We only collect personal information for a child under 13 where that students school, district, teacher, parent or guardian has agreed to obtain parental consent for the child to use these services. If you are a child under 13 and have not obtained consent, do not use this service until you have received consent. You may only use specified sections within this website with consent from your teacher, school, district, parent or guardian.
  9. #### Policy Amendments

    1. We may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes
  10. #### Your Rights

    1. You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information will be subject to: 
      1. the payment of a fee (currently fixed at CAD $20)
and 
      2. the supply of appropriate notarized evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a notary or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address)
    2. We may withhold such personal information to the extent permitted by law.
    3. You may instruct us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes, by sending an email to us. In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes.
  11. #### Third Party Websites

    1. The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third-parties
  12. #### Content

    1. This service contains personal information uploaded by users and enterprises. We are not responsible for the content, nor privacy policies nor practices of the third-parties providing that information
  13. #### Updating Information

    1. Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated
  14. #### Cookies

    1. A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.
    2. We use "persistent" cookies on the service. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.
    3. We will use persistent cookies to enable our service to recognize you (as distinct from other users) when you visit and keep track of your preferences in relation to your use of our website.
    4. We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of the service. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about service use by means of cookies, which are stored on users computers. The information generated relating to the service is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
    5. Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of this any many other services.
  15. #### Contact

    1. If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please contact us
